# Harshul Satija

Diligent software engineer with 2 years of experience in business applications. Eager to get a software engineer internship or research opportunity. Skilled in developing plans, managing projects, and research.

1811 Canton Drive Milpitas, CA (925)-663-5895

satijaharshul55@gmail.com

# SKILLS AND PROFICIENCIES

- Java, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Pvthon, C++
- Teamwork, multitasking, and attention to detail
- Software and web development
- MS Office 2016, Photoshop, Adobe, Publisher, Word, Video Editing
- Interpersonal Skills: Creative thinker, Leader, Public Speaking, Responsible, Motivational

#### **ADDITINAL INFORMATION**

 Certificate & Achievements: NAF: Be Future Ready certification, Flex Factor Silicon Valley Finals(3rd place), Crash Course on Python (Google)

#### **LANGUAGES**

- American English (Native)
- Hindi(C2 Level)
- Spanish (B1 Level)

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## Verizon/Deloitte Technology Intern

Verizon | July 2020 - August 2020

Researched, designed, and implemented machine learning and artificial intelligence to solve Model UN's goal. Researched and developed new ways to improve development process. Coded a website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery languages.

#### NextFlex (Intern)

Product Development | Dec 2020- Jan 2021

Used critical thinking to break down problems, evaluate solutions, and make decisions. Performed research to assist in full development process. Performed statistical, qualitative and quantitative analysis. Planned, modified executed research techniques, procedures, and tests.

### Milpitas High School

Cafeteria Worker | August 2019-June 2022

Assisted cashiers with processing customer payments and documenting orders. Managed deliveries and assisted with carrying out orders to promote maximum satisfaction. Collected and authorized payments.

#### University of California, Merced

Cafeteria Worker | August 2022 - November 2022

Cleaned and sanitized surfaces, Served food according to temperature, safety, and presentation guidelines. Provided exemplary service to service to students, staff and visitors. Cooked food per recipe requirements in large batches for routine school breakfast, lunches, and dinners.

# **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

# High School Diploma

Milpitas High School | 2018 - 2022 Milpitas, CA

Bachelor of Science | Computer Science & Engineering University of California, Merced | 2022- Present Merced, CA